<?xml version="1.1" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<databaseChangeLog xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
                   xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                   xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-4.2.xsd">

    <!-- ChangeSet for adding users -->
    <changeSet author="your_author" id="unique-id-for-adding-users" labels="version-0.0.1">

        <sql>
            INSERT INTO company (company_id, company_name, industry, website, description, contacts, socials, company_url_path, company_img_path)
            VALUES
                (1, "Google", "Technology", "https://www.google.com", "Google is a multinational technology company that specializes in Internet-related services and products. It is known for its search engine, online advertising technologies, cloud computing, software, and hardware.", "https://support.google.com", "Follow Google on Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn", "google", "/assets/img/clients/google.png"),
                (2, "Apple Inc.", "Technology", "https://www.apple.com", "Apple Inc. is an American multinational technology company that designs, manufactures, and markets consumer electronics, software, and services. It's known for products like the iPhone, Mac, and iPad.", "https://www.apple.com", "Connect with Apple on Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn", "apple","/assets/img/clients/apple.png"),
                (3, "Microsoft", "Technology", "https://www.microsoft.com", "Microsoft is a global technology company that develops, licenses, and sells computer software, consumer electronics, and personal computers. It's known for Windows, Office, and Azure.", "https://support.microsoft.com", "Join Microsoft on Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn", "microsoft","/assets/img/clients/microsoft.png"),
                (4, "Amazon", "Technology", "https://www.amazon.com", "Amazon is a multinational technology and e-commerce company. It is the world's largest online sales platform and a leading cloud computing provider through Amazon Web Services.", "https://www.amazon.com", "Follow Amazon on Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn", "amazon", "/assets/img/clients/amazon.png"),
                (5, "Meta", "Technology", "https://www.facebook.com", "Facebook is a social media and technology company. It's known for its social networking platform and services like Instagram, WhatsApp, and Oculus VR.", "https://www.facebook.com", "Connect with Facebook on Twitter, Instagram, and LinkedIn", "facebook","/assets/img/clients/meta.png"),
                (6, "Oracle Corporation", "Technology", "https://www.oracle.com", "Oracle Corporation is a global technology company that specializes in database software, cloud computing, and enterprise software. It provides database solutions and cloud services.", "https://www.oracle.com", "Join Oracle on Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn", "oracle","/assets/img/clients/Oracle-logo.png");
        </sql>

    </changeSet>

</databaseChangeLog>
